http://www.westernstatesenvelope.com/privacy-policy

Jump to Navigation
xVisit our Blog and Subscribe!
x
Need to brand your own flyer?
As a wholesale supplier, we understand that our customers prefer to market our products with their own brand. To do so is simple:
Download the PDF.
Open it in Adobe Illustrator or Adobe Photoshop and add your logo.
OR simply open the flyer up your PDF reader and enter in your information into the fields at the bottom of the page.
That's it! You can then print it or send it in an email to your customers.
About
Envelopes 101BasicsStylesStandard SizesSeals and ClosuresSeams and FlapsGlossary
Stock ProductsCommercialsCatalogs/BookletsAnnouncements/InvitationsOffice ProductsNew ProductsView Catalog
CapabilitiesStock ProductsCustom ProductsSpecial OperationsPrintingConverting
Resources for ResultsCustomizable FlyersEnvelope TemplatesCustomer ManagementCase StudiesPostal InformationWhite Papers/Education
Labels 101Resource GuideDimensionsLabel CharacteristicsLabel Glossary
ProductsPressure Sensitive LabelsShapes and StylesAdhesivesLaser Label SheetsLarge Laser Label SheetsIntegrated LabelsFace Stocks
Label CapabilitiesLaser Die CuttingConventional Die CuttingPrintingFinishing / Packaging
Resources for ResultsLabel TemplatesCustom CreationsCustomer ManagementCase Studies
EnvelopesEnvelope Artwork GuidelinesEnvelope TemplatesMeasuring an EnvelopeFlat Sheet/Converting
LabelsLabel Artwork GuidelinesLabel Templates & DiesMeasuring LabelsStandard Colors
Files & FormatsAccepted File FormatsSend Us Your FilesVector vs. Raster Files
Our Passion for PreservationCoC CertificationsBenefits of PaperIdeas and Tips for Recycling
Eco-Friendly ProductsRecycled EnvelopesReusable Envelopes
Product VideosDigi-Clear Heat-Safe WindowsTear-ific EnvelopesCustom LabelsEcoEnvelopeseKEY Mailers - Disc MailersView More...
Corporate VideosCustom Solutions. Proven Results.Corporate Tour2013 PEAK AwardsSee Western States Envelope in 1941View More...
All Video
Contact UsStay ConnectedEmail or Call UsHoliday Closings
About UsCustomer TestimonialsThe Western States DifferenceCommitment to QualityHistoryAwardsCommunity Outreach
LocationsCorporate HeadquartersEnvelope Facility LocationsLabel Division
Western States NewsThe Wrap - A BlogPress ReleasesIndustry EventsIndustry News
You are hereHome›Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We at Western States Envelope care about your privacy.  We want to explain in detail our policies and procedures which we have adopted in order to protect your privacy.  We want you to feel confident about how we handle personal information (your name, address, telephone number, credit card number and e-mail address) which you have shared with us and to understand that this information is used to offer you the best possible products, services, experiences, to enter contests/sweepstakes, and participate in promotions/postings or receive samples.
Below is a summary of our privacy policy but, please do take the time to read the policy in detail in the following pages.
We have not or will not share any of your personal information with outside parties without your consent.  We will use your personal information to fulfill your requests and to serve you better.
We will only send you information or products we feel are relevant and useful to your business. Of course, we will honor your opt-out requests.
When you visit the site for the first time, you will be asked to grant us permission to collect information through the use of cookies and web beacons to help us understand how our customers are using the Web site and to provide better functionality, as well as offering you personalized content.
We continue to adopt careful and secure procedures to protect any and all of your personal information.  Special care is taken to protect any credit card data you provide when you shop online.
We reserve the right to use or disclose your personal information in certain circumstances, such as to satisfy a legal request or to protect our property.
Changes in our policy
While we do not anticipate a need to change this privacy policy very often, we reserve the right to change or replace this policy at our discretion.  We invite you to visit this privacy policy area often to ensure you are aware of any changes or updates to this policy.
Consent to this privacy policy
By providing Western States Envelope with personal information, you are signifying that you do agree with the terms of this privacy policy.  If you do not agree with any terms of this policy, please do not submit any personal information or use this site.  If you choose not to submit any personal information, you may be denied access to particular areas of the Web site and/or from entering sweepstakes/contests, requesting samples, or sending us an e-mail.
Personal information collected and how we use that information
We collect personal information from you (i.e. name, address, phone number, e-mail address, activity information, interests and the like) when you voluntarily provide it to us.
Depending on the reason the information was provided, we may use the information to communicate with you about our products, services, promotions, and to provide information you have requested.  We may also use it to make improvements to our product or services.
You may be prompted to submit personal information in order to:
Register for a sweepstakes, contest or other promotions
Register on our Web site
To participate in surveys and/or a consumer research committee
To receive samples
Purchase products online including your credit card information
E-mail you with news and updates, and/or to respond to your questions, comments or concerns
Receive a newsletter or other material from us, and/or
We may ask if you would want to receive information about other Western States Envelope products.
Western States Envelope Web site viewers participation in any of these aforementioned activities (and therefore the provision of personal information) is completely voluntary.  We will not send anyone any newsletter or E-mail communications, unless we have your consent.  We offer our customers the option to cease receiving any of our E-mails at any time by notifying us by E-mail.
How we use cookies and Web beacons
A cookie is a data file that is placed on your computer while you are visiting the Web site. These data files allow us to remember vital information that will enhance your experience and make the site more efficient, useful and make your visit as easy as possible. Information that may be kept track of would be IP address, type of browser, operating system, and pages viewed by the user on our site and other sites visited prior to ours.
Almost all browsers accept cookies automatically and the system can notify you when a cookie is being sent.  You will have to refer to your browser help menu to learn how to disable cookies.  Please keep in mind that if you disable cookies, you may not be able to access some of the features on our site.
Web beacons (known as one pixel GIF) are small pieces of computer code which allow us to count how many people visit our site or certain pages on the site or open an e-mail.
It allows us to better customize the Web site in order to personalize it and improve your experience while visiting. Cookies and Web beacons do not collect or contain personal information like your name or your e-mail address.
Information sharing
As mentioned earlier, at certain times we may share your personal information with other parties but, only if we have your consent.  The security of your personal information is a priority to us. We also may share this personal information to parties who provide services on our behalf. They will only be allowed to use information that directly applies to the service(s) they provide for us, and only for the purpose of providing the service(s). When we use these third parties we require them to protect your information just as we have done.
If we are asked to disclose any of the personal information to law enforcement agencies or if we are required by law, subpoena, court order or government entity, we must comply.  We may also have to disclose personal information to conduct an investigation if legal action is brought against someone violating the use of this site.
Credit Card/transaction information
We at Western States Envelope are committed to the safety and security of your transactions.  To aid us in the assurance of safety and security when using your credit card, we currently use SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology.  SSL uses the latest technology to create a secure connection from our computer to yours when making an order.  It makes it extremely difficult for anyone else to intercept your information.  Notwithstanding the use of SSL technology, Western States Envelope cannot guarantee the security of your transaction(s) on this Web site.
Links to other websites
We may offer links to other Web sites outside of our company.  We make our best efforts to link with those Web sites that share the same values as we do.   However, these Web sites should have their own privacy policies and in any event, are not be governed by this privacy policy.  We encourage you to read and review these third party privacy policies as we are not responsible for their content or information collection policies as they may treat their information differently.
How to Contact Us
If you should have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please E-mail us at webmaster@wsel.com. You may also reach us by telephone at 1-800-558-0514.
Get a Quote
Order Online
View Catalogs
Contact Us
Share / Print
Western States Envelope & Label
Facebook
Twitter
CORPORATE4480 N. 132nd Street Butler, WI 53007-2099 800-558-0514
OHIO6859 Commodore DriveWalbridge, OH 43465-9765800-835-3734
KENTUCKY1347 Jamike LaneErlanger, KY 41018-3115800-354-9806
MINNESOTA1239 Willow Lake Blvd., Ste 101Vadnais Heights, MN 55110-5145800-366-1721
LABEL DIVISION861 Progress WaySun Prairie, WI 53590-9571800-798-7989
